In case you get any ideas about following us.
防止你试图跟踪我们
Eugene!
尤金
I'm so sorry. Everything is going to be okay, though.
真对不起 一切都会好起来的
No, Rapunzel.
不 长发公主
I promise. You have to trust me. Come on. Just breathe.
我保证 相信我 快 挺住
I can't let you do this.
我不能让你这么做
And I can't let you die.
我不能看着你死掉
But if you do then you will die.
但你这么做 你就会死的
Hey. It's going to be all right.
嘿 一切都会好起来的
Rapunzel.
长发公主
Wait.
等一下
Eugene...
尤金
No!
不
What have you done? What have you done?
你都干了什么 你都干了什么
No!
不
No! No. No!
不 不 不
No, no, no. Eugene.
不 不 不要 尤金
No! Look at me. I'm right here. Don't go. Stay with me.
不 看着我 我在这儿 不要离开我 挺住
Flower, gleam and glow Let your power shine
魔花闪烁 借汝之力
Make the clock reverse Bring back what once was mine
闪回时间 还我容颜
Rapunzel.
长发公主
What?
什么
You were my new dream.
你就是我的新梦想
And you were mine.
你也是我的
Heal what has been hurt
治愈伤痛
Change the Fates' design
逆命而上
Save what has been lost
还吾所失
Bring back what once was mine
返吾本相
What once was mine
我的时光